A Guide to the Papers of the Jefferson National Bank ca. 1914-1998
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Advertising Material 1967-1997, n.d. (Carton 7-8 Also OS Boxes 1-12)
  - Teller Machine, Picture of n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Things To Do Dec 1-5: National Bank's Grand Opening at Pantops n.d., Advertising boards (2 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Thousands of Gardeners Count On Us To Help Their Money Grow. To Us, Every Week Is Garden Week (NBTC & Jefferson Bank of the Valley) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Totally Satisfying Banking (JNB)--Experience It!--We Promise! n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - University of Virginia Adverstisement--We've Got You Covered! (NB) 1983 Sep, Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - When You're Out And About Tomorrow Taking Care of Business, Be Sure To Include A Stop At National Bank's New Pantops Office (NB) 1980 Nov 25, Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - With 5 1/4% Interest Across The Board, Nobody's Been Looking After Your Interest Checking Better Than Your Own Bank (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - You're Invited to Try Out Hovey Dabney's New Video Game--Just Bring One of These n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - You Can Count On Us (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - You Can Count On Us To Pay The Highest Rate on 6-Month Money Market Certificates Allowed By Law n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - After-Christmas CHRISTMAS Club--Enroll now... Start saving the end of January n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - Banking at Your Fingertips:--24-Hour Most Automated Teller--Banking Convenience and Free Movie Tickets n.d., Advertising boards (1 brochure and 1 advertisement) (Oversize 1)
  - Board with Checkbook and Pen n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - Buttons: --"Customers are Good For Business"--What the best bankers in town will be wearing this year --"You Can Count On Me" n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - The Cavalier Daily--Locations of NTBC Branches, including a detailed map of the University of Virginia 1979 Aug 28, Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - Christmas Replay, IRA Let Us Pray, IRA Smart Play, IRA n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - A Freshman's First Test: Finding the Right Bank for the Next Four Years n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - Happy Day, IRA Less To Pay With IRA Save The Day, IRA n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - Louisa Opening Advertisement--Make Our New Bank Your New Bank n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - National Bank Goes Them One Better! Now... Free Personal and Business Checking Accounts n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - Opening of Mineral Office--"Great Day!" n.y. Jan 21, Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - Phil Morton Has Never Fought A Fire, But These Men Count On Him To Keep From Getting Burned n.d., Advertising boards (2 copies) (Oversize 1)
  - Roger Shifflet Won A Position On The Piedmont Little League Because He Never Throws A Curve n.d., Advertising boards (2 copies) (Oversize 1)
  - Sign up for Club Service Banking--Get The Card With More Tellers 'Round The Grounds n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - This Year We're Pinning A Compliment On You n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - We're Counting On You: --Count On Us To Take The Bounce of Your Checks --Count On Us To Take The Bounce out of Your Checks. Ask About Ready Reserve 5 & 1/2%, 6%, 6 & 1/2%, 7 & 1/4%--Count On Us For High Interest Savings Certificates --When You Get That New Car Itch, Count On Us For The Scratch n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - --We Make Our Savings Plan Fit Your Life --We Make Our Auto Loans Fit Your Life n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 1)
  - NB-115, NB 152, NB 138: Response Advertisement 1978 May 12, Advertisements in envelopes with and without NB numbers (Oversize 1)
  - Response Advertisements 1976 Feb 23, Advertisements in envelopes with and without NB numbers (Oversize 1)
  - Social Security Newspaper n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with and without NB numbers (Oversize 1)
  - Banking Convenience and Free Moviet Tickets At Your Fingertips n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 1)
  - Banking Convenience at Your Fingertips--24-Hour Teller n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 1)
  - Diamonds Aren't Forever--Let's Pitch In To Build A New Ballpark n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 1)
  - Feel Free! (NTBC) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 1)
  - Financial Peace of Mind (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (2 copies) (Oversize 1)
  - If You're Confused By What Every Dick and Harry Bank Is Saying About Credit Lines, Come Talk To Tom (NB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 1)
  - Introducing... The New Mark of Progressive Banking In Central Virginia n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 1)
  - It Was The Solid Small Banks That Financed Virginia (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (2 copies) (Oversize 1)
  - The Jefferson Eagle Mobile n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 1)
  - Limited Edition Print of Thomas Jefferson (in his fifties) Painted by John Middleton Freeman 1993, Advertising posters (Oversize 1)
  - National Bank Has Always Been a Respected Name In Banking Changing Our Name Won't Change That (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 1)
  - People Are Saying YES! To Jefferson National's Blue Ribbon Loans (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (2 copies) (Oversize 1)
  - Self Stick Logos And Names Of Jefferson National Bank n.d., Advertising posters (12 items) (Oversize 1)
  - A Simple Comparison Between National Bank & A Savings & Loan (NB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 1)
  - Smart Play, IRA (Southern Bank) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 1)
  - Uniquely Superior--The Jefferson Eagle (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (2 copies) (Oversize 1)
  - Confused by New Interest Rates? Let's Look at the Facts (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Count On Us To Take Some of the Hassle Out of Your First Week of School (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - The Financial Picture For Your Retirement May Not Be Clear--Our Advice On Retirement Plans Is (Jefferson Bank of the Valley & First National Bank of Luray) n.d., Advertising boards (2 copies) (Oversize 2)
  - Financial Peace of Mind--Important Words For An Important Feeling (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Financial Peace of Mind--It's A Special Going Home Feeling (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - 5 & 1/2 % Savings Certificate (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Have Your Played the Greatest Video Game in Town? (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Here's Your Golden Opportunity To Try A Bank That Offers Some Things You Can Believe In n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Here's Your Golden Opportunity To Try A Bank That Offers Some Things You Can Believe In n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - If You Think Credit Lines Are For The Rich, How Do You Think They Got That Way? (JNB) 1989 Jun 9, Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - If You Think Some People Are Crazy To Pull Equity Out of Their House, There Are Those Who Would Agree With You (JNB) 1989 Jun 9, Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Introducing Our New 24-Hour Tellers (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Louisa or Mineral Office (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - NB-273: Counter Card Stuffer--5%, 5 1/2%, 6% 6 1/2%, 7 1/4%--Count On Us For The Maximum Interest Rates On Savings Allowed By Law n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - NBT-143: We Make Our Banking Hours Fit Your Life n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - NO--No Limit To The Number of Checks You Can Write (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Perma Cash: Take A Bite Out of Rising Finance Charges n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Photographs of Stuarts Draft Office (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Photographs of West End Office Branch (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Pictures For Fireman Advertisement--"Phil Morton Has Never Fought A Fire.. ." (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Retirement Planning For The Self-Employed (NB Corporation) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Some Credit Lines Just Won't Pan Out The Way You Thought They Would (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - The $30,000,000 We Have To Lend Will Only Go So Far n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - We'll Bet You A Gallon of Gas Our Bank is Closer Than Your Bank (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - What Can We Do To Announce Saturday Banking From 9 to Noon at National Bank's Mineral Office? (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Why Our Interest Checking Is Bound To Be The Best In 25 Words or Less (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (3 copies) (Oversize 2)
  - With Perma Cast, This Is All You Have To Fill Out For A Loan. (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (2 copies) (Oversize 2)
  - Your Commercial Checking Account (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 2)
  - Customers Are Good For Business Campaign--Photographs of (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Confused by New Interest Rates? Let's Look at The Facts (NBTC) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - The confusion About All Savers Certificates Started Here--It Ends Here (NB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Don't Misplace Your Trust--Personal Trust Services (NBTC) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Get In Touch With Real Banking Convenience--24-Hour Most Automated Teller (NB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - If You Think Credit Lines Are Only For The Rich, How Do You Think They Got That Way? (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - If You Think Some People Are Crazy To Pull Equity Out of Their Houses, There Are Those Who Would Agree With You (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (2 copies) (Oversize 2)
  - If You're Confused By What Every Dick and Harry Bank Is Saying About Credit Lines, Come Talk To Tom (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Introducing... The New Mark of Progressive Banking In Central Virginia (NBTC) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Jefferson's Protect A Purchase Checking--Before Something Valuable You Buy Gets Cracked (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Joint Resolution of the Boards of Directors of Jefferson Bankshares, Inc. and Jefferson National Bank 1997 Jun 17, Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Knowing Where You're Going Starts Right Here (NBTC) n.d., Advertising posters (2 copies) (Oversize 2)
  - The Leading Money Managers of Wall Street Are at Jefferson National Bank (JNB) 1989 Sep 19, Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Look For Us! Jefferson National Bank--Totally Satisfying Banking n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Make Our New Bank Your New Bank n.d., Advertising posters (2 copies) (Oversize 2)
  - NOW! New Longer Hours At These Offices--Emmet Street Office & The Blue Ridge Office (NBTC) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - The People's Bank of Stafford is NOW Jefferson National Bank (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Put Your Money In A Bank Where You Can Put Your Two Cents In, Too (NBTC) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - She's 4 1/2, He's 5 3/4 (NBTC) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - A Simple Interest Auto Loan Gives You More Flexibility (Southern Bank) n.d., Advertising posters (3 copies) (Oversize 2)
  - Some Credit Lines Just Won't Pan Out The Way You Thought They Would (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Ultra Yield: The Ultimate Savings Plan (NBTC) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Virginia Basketball, Come Sky With Us (Flight Schedule) 1988-1989, Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - We Interrupt This Newspaper For An Important Announcement (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - "When You Have A Lot of Steak, You Need a Bank That Won't Steer You Wrong" (NBTC) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - When The Car Has Had It And So Have You (NBTC) n.d., Advertising posters (Oversize 2)
  - Who Says You Can't Please All The People All The Time! (JNB) n.d., Advertising posters (2 copies) (Oversize 2)
  - You Can Count On National Bank Where You Count! (NB) n.d., Advertising posters (2 copies) (Oversize 2)
  - Illustration of an Unidentified National Bank's Office Branch n.d., Photographs and illustrations for advertisements (Oversize 2)
  - Photograph Shoots of "The Financial Peace of Mind" Advertisement (JNB) n.d., Photographs and illustrations for advertisements (Oversize 2)
  - Photographs of National Bank's Staff For Advertisements n.d., Photographs and illustrations for advertisements (3 photographs) (Oversize 2)
  - Photograph of Class of 1978 of the School of Banking of the South 1978 Jun 2, Photographs and illustrations for advertisements (Oversize 2)
  - Picture For Jefferson National Bank's Advertisement... "Some Credit Lines Just Won't Pan Out The Way You Thought They Would" n.d., Photographs and illustrations for advertisements (Oversize 2)
  - Picture of An Unidentified Office Branch National Bank and Trust Company n.d., Photographs and illustrations for advertisements (Oversize 2)
  - Add Checking Plus To Your Banking (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - A Bank, But Not A Stuffy Bank (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Drive In (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Fight Vacation Inflation!--Go For The Fun of It With Our Bank Club 10% Travel Savings n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Fishersville, US Route 250--Temporary Identification & Proposed Future Identification n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Guardian Account (NBTC) 1978 Oct 27, Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Guess What Just Popped Up In Tidewater? (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - If You're At Least This Age And Bank At Sovran, Crestar, Signet, Dominion or Central Fidelity, You're Old Enough To Know Better--The Jefferson Edge (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Interest Checking Is A Checking Account & A Savings Account (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Jefferson National Bank Charlottesville Office Hours & Locations n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - NB-110: Put Your Two Cents Here n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - NB-273: 5%, 5 1/2%, 6 % 6 1/2%, 7 1/4%--Count On Us For The Maximum Interest Rates on Savings Allowed By Law n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - NB-142: We Make Our Banking Hours Fit Your Life (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - NBT-160: Confused by New Interest Rates? Let's Look at the Facts n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - NBT-180: There's nobody else (Savings & Investment Certificate Advertisement) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Officers & Charlottesville Offices, Officers & Rural Offices or Advisory Boards (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Safe Deposit Boxes (NB) 1981 Sep 14, Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - 6%, 6 1/2% Investment Certificates 1976 Aug 18, Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Social Security Direct Deposit (NBTC) 1976 Nov, Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Statement of Condition (NB) 1985 Mar 31, Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Ultra Yield--The Ultimate Savings Plan 1973 Jul, Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - The Understandable Bank Statement (NBTC) 1972 Jan, Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - We'll Bet You A Gallon of Gas Our Bank Is Closer Than Your Bank (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 3)
  - Downtown Mall, Charlottesville NBTC Office n.d., Photographs for advertisements (Oversize 3)
  - Emmet Street Office n.d., Photographs for advertisements (Oversize 3)
  - Fork Union Office (NBTC) n.d., Photographs for advertisements (Oversize 3)
  - Ivy Road Office (NBTC) n.d., Photographs for advertisements (Oversize 3)
  - Mineral Office n.d., Photographs for advertisements (Oversize 3)
  - New Hope Office n.d., Photographs for advertisements (Oversize 3)
  - Palmyra Office n.d., Photographs for advertisements (Oversize 3)
  - The Piedmont Little League & Roger Shifflet for National Bank advertisement n.d., Photographs for advertisements (Oversize 3)
  - Scottsville Flood, One near Watson's Market, and the other unidentified ca. 1972, Photographs for advertisements (2 photographs) (Oversize 3)
  - Scottsville Office n.d., Photographs for advertisements (Oversize 3)
  - A Social Security Card for National Bank Advertisement, photographs n.d., Photographs for advertisements (Oversize 3)
  - West End Office n.d., Photographs for advertisements (Oversize 3)
  - NB-110: Response Suggestion Box (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-111: Response Statement Stuffer (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-114 & NB-115: Response Advertisement, #1 & #2 (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-116: Employee Motivation Package (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-118: University of Virginia Student Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-134: Call Charlottesville Introduction Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-135: Call Charlottesville Follow-Up Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-144: Garden Week Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-152: Garden Week Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-159 & NB-164: Madison Mortgage Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-164: Lovingston Mailer (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-165: Barracks Road Opening (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 4)
  - NB-170: New Hope Mailer (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-174: University of Virginia Advertisements and Maps (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (one map without envelope) (Oversize 5)
  - NB-178: Checking Account Enclosure (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-179: Savings Teller Handout (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-180: Passbook Dry Stick (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-182: Statement Savings Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-184: Tax Reform Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-187: Madison Branch Opening (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-190: Louisa Temp. Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-191: Dabney Brochure (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-192: Lovingston Premium Mailer (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-194: Mortgage Classified Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-198: Savings Interest Card (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 5)
  - NB-203: Ready Reserve Brochure (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 6)
  - NB-204: Ready Reserve Counter Card (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 6)
  - NB-205: Ready Reserve Announcement Ad (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 6)
  - NB-214: Checking Plus Brochure (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 6)
  - NB-217: $5 Safety Deposit Box Certificate (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 6)
  - NB-218: Family Savings Certificate (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 6)
  - NB-219: Checking Plus Kit Folder (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 6)
  - NB-221: Checking Plus Newspaper Ad (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 6)
  - NB-229: Checking Plus Follow-up Ad (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 6)
  - NB-230: Ready Reserve Follow-up Ad (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 6)
  - NB-238: 1979 Calendar Heading (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 6)
  - NB-245: Loan Campaign (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-247: Checking Plus In-Bank Cards (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-249: Treasury Bill Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-252: Map Advertisement (NBTC) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-257: Louisa Opening Advertisement (NB) 1978 Nov 10, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-261: Ready Reserve Cover (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-265: Employee Kit (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-267: Employee Buttons n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-268: Rural Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-268A: Rural Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-268B: Rural Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-268C: Rural Advertisement (NB) n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 7)
  - NB-269: Roger Shifflet Advertisement (NB) 1979 Jan 29, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 8)
  - NB-270: Phil Morton Advertisement (NB) 1979 Jan 29, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 8)
  - NB-273: Savings Rate Change Materials (NB) n.y. Mar 6, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 8)
  - NB-275: Treasury Bill Rate Change Advertisement (NB) 1979 Apr 12, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 8)
  - NB-280: Savings Announcement Advertisement (NB) 1979 Jun 18, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 8)
  - NB-283: Newcomer's Advertisement (NB) 1979 Jul-Aug, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 8)
  - NB-288: Jefferson Bankshares Direct Mail (NB) 1979 Sep 4, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 8)
  - NB-289: Jefferson Bankshares Advertisement (NBTC) 1979 Sep 21, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 9)
  - NB-290: Garden Week Advertisement (NBTC) 1979 Sep 24, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 9)
  - NB-295: Pantops Opening Statement Stuffer (NB) 1979 Dec 27, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 9)
  - Gillum Campaign--Photographs, Boards and Posters n.d., Advertisements in envelopes without NB numbers (Oversize 9)
  - Annual Report Advertisements 1981, Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 9)
  - Jefferson Bankshares, Inc. Brochures n.d., Advertisements in envelopes with NB numbers (Oversize 9)
  - Original Newspaper Advertisements (NB) 1971-1982 (Oversize 10)
  - At Jefferson National Bank, We Do Whatever It Takes To Keep You Totally Satisfied 100 Percent of The Time (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 11)
  - The Balance of Power--The Jefferson National Line (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 11)
  - Dividends Visa Card--Put A Little Freedom In Your Pocket (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 11)
  - For Over 80 Years, Four Generations of Stuarts Depended On Jefferson National Bank (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Oversize 11)
  - 1,232 Employees of Jefferson Nation Bank Pledge To Keep You Totally Satisfied--We Care!--We Promise! n.d., Advertising boards (2 copies) (Oversize 11)
  - Perma Cash Brochure (NB) 1984 Dec 19, Advertising boards (3 pieces) (Oversize 11)